Guide to the Papers of Abby Weed Grey 1922-1978 MC 151
New York University Archives
- Series V: Artist Files
  - Subseries F: Turkey
    - Sergisi, Resim, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Series VI: Index Cards, 1947-1978
  Contains notes and ideas on poetry, articles, poems, journal entries, and quotations. They are arranged chronologically.
  - Index Cards, Jan 1947-Aug 1947 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Index Cards, Dec 1948-Oct 1949 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Index Cards, Sep 1953-Jan 1954 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Index Cards, Jan 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Index Cards, Jan 1957-Nov 1957 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Index Cards, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Index Cards, Jan 1959-Dec 1959 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Index Cards, Jan 1960-Feb 1960, 1961 Feb (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Index Cards, May 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Index Cards, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Series VII: Misc. Activities and Memorabilia, 1959-1975
  Contains interview transcripts, course notes, questions, speeches, lectures, notes, drafts, published materials, calendars, notes, correspondence, invoices, biographical information on Mrs. Grey, personal cards, clippings, and drawings.
  - Taped Interview with self (Sets 1-54), 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Taped Interview with self (Sets 1-54)-Edited, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Course on Contemporary Art Questions (Index cards), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Lecture to Women's Club-Draft, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Lecture: New Century Club- Draft & Notes, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - "A Study in Genealogy" *See Separation Box, Fldr. 5, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - River Stories, Agnes Weed Stoddard Johnson, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Calendars, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Notes on film "Norma Milburn", 1971 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Abby Weed Grey Interview Transcript, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Notes on course "Iran in Black & White," by Sam Peterson, undated (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Minneapolis Society of Fine Arts, misc., undated (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, undated (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Clippings on "Shah & Iran", 1967 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Child's Drawing, undated (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Valentine from Peter, undated (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Abby Weed Grey Biography (up to 1971), undated (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Ellen Johnson Gallery of Modern Art, undated (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings & Publicity, undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
- Series VIII: Correspondence
  Contains personal and professional correspondence arranged alphabetically by author or subject. Materials consist of information regarding memberships, art, artists, contributions, family history, Vassar College, financial documents, invoices, telegrams, clippings, purchases, and Parviz Tanavoli.
  - Ahmad, Sayeed, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225389 1
  - Bartlett ancestor, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cogswell, Margaret, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cousin Eloise, Jan 1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Damarind College (Iran), 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Deqhani-Tafti, Hassan (Bishop)-Notes from letters, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Deqhani-Tafti, Hassan (Bishop) - Letters, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Eren, Cemil, 1970-1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Ettinghausen, Richard (Parviz' rugs), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Farmanfaarmain, Abolbashar, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Films (including Corke films), undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Gebara, Raymond, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gregory, Jane (Photog), 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Grey Foundation/Grey museum, Jul 1972-May 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Khaghani, Jamshid, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Kilic, Altemur, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Liston, Glenn, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Milkovich, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, Jul 1962-Dec 1962 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, Jan 1963-Mar 1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, Aug 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, Jan 1964-Jun 1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, Jul 1964-Dec 1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Mitchell, Geraldine, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Poems (MacMillan Co, Publ.), 1945 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Poetry, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Seichrist, Ron *See Photo Collection, Box 4, Fldr 16, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sherman, Elisabeth, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Tehran Museum, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Textile Museum, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Turkish Art Today, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Weed, Emmy Lu, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Whorra, Raveesh, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Winkler, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Series IX: Tanavoli, Parviz
  Arranged alphabetically by subject. Personal and professional correspondence (most of correspondence is from P. Tanavoli, and has been recopied or typed out, also correspondence is to P. Tanavoli, and to and from his wife Janet), clippings, financial and personal records, catalogs, brochures regarding artist's work, and invoices.
  - Catalogs/Brochures *See Separation Box, Fldrs. 6-8, 1957-1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Clippings, 1959-1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence (Janet Tanavoli), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), Mar 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), Sep 1975-Nov 1976 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), Jan 1977-Sep 1978 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (type copy), 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (Originals), 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence from Parviz (typed copy), 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence to Parviz, 1969-1970, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Financial Records, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Galloway, David (Re: Book on Parviz), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Minneapolis School of Art, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Personal Records, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - "Prophet, The", Sculpture, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Venice Biennale, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Series X: Grey Gallery and Study Center NYU, 1970-1977
  - Chelkowski, Peter (Origins of Gift: NYU), 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - NYU Proposal for Art Gallery & Study Center, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Initial Selections, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Contextual Placement of Gallery Notes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NYU "Woman of Achievement Award" (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NYU/Gallery: "Berkman Proposal", 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Gallery Catalog Draft, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gallery Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "My Search for the Unknown Artist...", 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "Lion Rug" Exhibit, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - NY Trips - Notes, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Legal Correspondence, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Floor Plans, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Inaugural Exhibition: Artist List, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Inaugural Invitation, Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Series XI: The University of Minnesota
  All materials are in regards to the 1973 proposal of establishing the Grey museum at the University of Minnesota. These materials include professional and personal correspondence, architectural plans, and meeting minutes of the Grey Foundation.
  - Correspondence on Grey Museum, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    3 1142 04225390 9
  - Architectural Plans for Grey Museum, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Grey Foundation/University of Minn. Negotiations, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Clippings, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Series XII: The Grey Foundation 1967-1969
  Materials are arranged in chronological order. Materials include personal and professional correspondence, clippings, film narrations, invitations, invoices, meeting minutes, and progress reports. The bulk are from 1967.
  - University of Utah: Benjamin Grey Memorial Lecture, 1957-1967 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Bronze Foundry at University of Teheran, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - National College of Arts Gift-Pakistan, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - University of Teheran Library Gift, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Gift: Exhibition of Student Sculptures, Teheran, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Foundry, 1st Student Exhibit, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Tanavoli Bronze to MOMA, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Film: "Poet/Philosopher", 1968 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Grey Foundation Miscellaneous Minutes, Reports, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Series XIII: Grey Foundation Exhibits 1961-1972
  Materials in this series are arranged chronologically. Materials include professional and personal correspondence, invitations, clippings, catalogs (in English and other languages), scrapbooks (separated and located in Box 8), financial information, invoices, photographs (separated and located in Photo Collection), itineraries, reports, and notes.
  - M.A.P. Itinerary, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Communication Through Art, Proposal, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Communication Through Art, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Communication Through Art, Proposal, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Communication Through Art, Proposal (edited), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Communication Through Art, Correspondence Re:Proposal, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Communication Through Art, Scrapbook *See Box 8, Fldr 3, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - 14 Contemporary Iranian Painters *See Box 8, Fldr 4, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Communication Through Art, Catalogs, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Communication Through Art, Report to USIS, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), West. Assoc. Art Museums, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Publicity, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Working Papers, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Artist Info, undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Turkish Art Today (Organization), Customs & Bills, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Communication Thru Art, Turkish Art Today, Scrapbook *See Box 8, Fldr 5, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Two Decades of American Painting, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 1st Triennale, India, Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Contemporary Japanese Wood Block Prints, 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225392 5
  - Contemporary Art of India and Iran *See Box 8, Fldr 6, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Contemporary Art of India and Iran, Smithsonian, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1st Triennale of World Art, India, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Communication Through Art, Indian Tour, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Communication Through Art, S. India *See Separation Box, Fldr 9, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "20 Prints", Minn. State Arts Council, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "Young Americans", Bogota, Columbia, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - SWANA Exhibit, SUNY Binghamton, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Communication Through Art, India, Book Presentation, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 10 Young Artists, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Works Shipped (To or from Iran?), Jul 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Minneapolis College of Art & Design (MCAD) Exhibit, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Contemporary Turkish Painting, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Aquatennial Exhibit, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - One World Through Art, Minn. State Fair *See Box 8, Fldrs 7-10, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - One World Through Art, Minn. State Fair *See Box 8, Fldrs 7-10, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibitions, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibitions, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibitions, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Series XIV: Scrapbooks
  This series comprises multi-medium materials such as photographs, news clippings, clipped catalogs, and pen and pencil on paper notes.
  - Notes on St. Mark's Cathedral Church, John Dewey (From Box 1, Fldr. 32, Series II: Unpublished Works), undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225393 3
  - Shabazi, Shahrokh (From Box 4, Fldr. 63, Series V: Artist Files, Subseries IV: Iran), undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Communication Through Art (From Box 6, Fldr. 42, Series XIII: Grey Foundation Exhibits 1961-72), 1961-1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Contemporary Iranian Painters (From Box 6, Fldr. 43, Series XIII), 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Communication Thru Art, Turkish Art Today, (From Box 6, Fldr. 52, Series XIII), 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Contemporary Art of India and Iran (From Box 7, Fldr. 2, Series XIII), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - One World Through Art, Minn. State Fair, India (From Box 7, Fldr. 16, Series XIII), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - One World Through Art, Minn. State Fair, Iran (From Box 7, Fldr. 16, Series XIII), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - One World Through Art, Minn. State Fair, Japan, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - One World Through Art, Minn. State Fair, Turkey (From Box 7, Fldr. 16, Series XIII), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Tanavoli Exhibition, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Series XV: Oversized Materials
  - Travel Diary (1st) * From Box 3, Fldr. 11, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225394 1
  - Travel Diary (original & edited) * From Box 3, Fldr. 13, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Travel Diary (original, copy & edited)* From Box 3, Fldr. 18, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Spyropoulos, Jannis *See Box 3, Fldr. 34, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "A Study in Genealogy" *See Box 4, Fldr. 93, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Poster (folded)-Tanavoli, Parviz sculpture exhibit *See Box 5, Fldr. 37, Apr 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Catalog-Parviz Tanavoli Bronze Sculpture *See Box 5, Fldr. 37, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Journal-"Art Internat'l w/The Lugano Review (See pg. 50) *See Box 5, Fldr. 37, Apr 1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Catalog-Ozzir Zuby, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Series XVI: Multimedia Collection
  This multimedia collection has been separated out into 4 boxes (3 paige boxes and one large archival box - approximately 5 feet of material). The collection consists of reel to reel tapes of 3", 5", 7", and larger sizes and cassette tapes. The reel to reel tapes of sizes 7" and smaller have been removed from their original non-archival boxes and re-housed in acid free boxes and sleeves. They have been labeled according to the information provided on their original boxes. In some instances more in-depth information regarding the content of the materials are included with the reels and tapes. No material has been separated.
  - Philip, Jean-Marc Masowsky, Shirley Goldfarb, Gregory Masowky, Apr 1967 (Box 10, Reel 1)
    3 1142 04225395 8
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    3" reel 1.5 mil acetate backing, 150 feet
  - Parviz Slides, Jul 1967 (Box 10, Reel 2, Disc 1)
    3" reel
  - Peg, Pierce, 1967 September 15 (Box 10, Reel 3)
  - Poetry ? (one side only), undated (Box 10, Reel 4)
    3" reel 1.5 mil acetate, 150 ft.
  - Recorder, undated (Box 10, Reel 5)
  - Poetry for Ursula, undated (Box 10, Reel 6)
  - Peg 8/9/67, Brewster Hayes, Pres. Cole, 1967 August-July (Box 10, Reel 7)
  - E.L.'s talk to century, undated (Box 10, Reel 8)
  - 1.) Pierce, Peg telephone re: Allen Weller & AFA 2.)Cancel - (speech), undated (Box 10, Reel 9)
    3" reel .65 mil tensilized polyester, 300 ft.
  - 1 of 3 reels taken from a 5" reel when needed an empty 12/13/67 - ? contents, 1967 (Box 10, Reel 10)
  - 2 of 3 reels taken from a 5" reel when needed an empty 12/13/67 - ? contents, 1967 (Box 10, Reel 11)
  - 3 of 3 reels taken from a 5" reel when needed an empty 12/13/67 - ? contents, 1967 (Box 10, Reel 12)
  - 1.) Peg C. '63-June 5? 2.) Pierce, 1963 (Box 10, Reel 13)
  - From Abby Weed Grey to Mrs. P.C. Weed, 477 Hudson St., NY, undated (Box 10, Reel 14)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 10, Reel 15)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 10, Reel 16)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 10, Reel 17)
  - Torn Film- Parviz Tanavoli, undated (Box 10, Reel 18)
  - Torn Film- Parviz Tanavoli 5" Reels, undated (Box 10, Reel 19)
  - 1.) Clara & AWG--telephone fall 1962, 2.) Pierce, Paul Scheffler, August 1964, 1962, August 1964 (Box 10, Reel 20)
  - Parviz Tanavoli, Sia, Barbara, 1964 May (Box 10, Folder 1)
    3" reel. This tape has been digitized.
  - 1.) Abby Weed Grey Poetry; Telephone-Parviz, Clara 1962 2.) Abby Weed Grey reads poetry; telephone-Max Lein, 1964, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    3" reel 1.5 mil acetate, 600 ft.
  - Chuck Ario-recorder June 17, 1965 Recorder and vocal-Winter 1965 Abby Weed Grey & Lois Brigham re: Turkish Collection release, 2/11/66, also Bryskin India show Brewster Ghesilin 2/13/66 from airport Lois, Peg about 9/20/65 re need for arts festival in Iran Pierce Sia calls about Parviz' letter, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    3" reel 1.5 mil. acetate, ft.
  - Abby Weed Grey-Turkey 1.) vacant, 2.) Turkey, consolidated, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1.) Barbara Manning 2.) Jane Rubin 6/1/66 Hilly & Abby Weed Grey 6/6/66 re attorney & Walker Jim Haseltine (his voice) Letter to Paul Schettler (slip inside) Iran cable; Inez Quin, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    3" reel 1.0 mil. acetate, 900 ft.
  - Empty Recorder Consort, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    3" reel 1/2 mil. mylar, 1200 ft.
  - TV Anchor Channel 2, Spring 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    3" reel 1.5 mil. acetate, 600 ft.
  - 1.) Poetry (dip in lake at Bala Nair), Sept. 1963 (?) Poetry reading Pierce & Illinois That's on my 1st talk on art at "U" (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Recorder Concert 3/66; Dean Mahyr-May 23, 1966; June 1966 (slip inside) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Bishop Dehqani-St. Matthews, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    3" reel plastic, 600 ft.
  - 1.) AWG 1971 2.) Abby Weed Grey 1975 re collection & Gallery, 1971, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 1.) Abby Weed Grey Poetry diary at Deer Lake Aug. 1964 Parviz ( part good) 2.) 1963 (crossed out) (See slip inside), 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - April 1966-2 cancel-speech (see slip inside for details), 1966 April (Box 10, Folder 13)
    3" reel .5 mil mylar, 1200 ft.
  - Peg - May 4, 1966, Sullivan - Fall1965 (see slip), 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Letter from Parviz to Sia, translated 1/3/65; Sia re: Pakkaz, Pilaram, and Fabrizi letters from Parviz (Sia, Mrs. Grey) Pierce comment re: Artists letter etc. 2/8/65, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 15, Disc 2, Disc 1)
    3" reel, 2 CDs
  - 1.) Abby Weed Grey & Bishop talk about the possibility of a "garden," how? 2.) Bishop Dehquani talk at Faubault about Sept. 2, 1963 ("A Still Small Voice" & prayer), Sep 1963 (Box 10, Folder 16, Disc 1, Disc 2)
  - "One World Thru Art"-opening June 16, 1972 Minnesota State Fair grounds gallery Interview with Abby Weed Grey (see slip inside), 1972 June (Box 10, Folder 17)
    3" reel 16mm, b/w TV newsclip
  - Deer Lake- Peg Cogswell & Abby Weed Grey conference no. 1, Aug. 29, 1964 (See slip inside with notes), 1964 August (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1.) Peg re: Bob Luck- April 1965 Paul Schettler- April 29, 1966 Jane & Abby Weed Grey, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1.) cogitations- Pierce diary Deer Lake Aug. 30th 2.) Inventory Deer Lake - "Comm. Thru Art", undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Aug. 1964 Telephone- Peg, Pierce, Paul Shettler, E.L., Pierce (Eldon), 1964 August (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - -E.L Read Lewis' talk to century club Fall 1965 on Fanny Kemble -copy of recorder concert in Galley Spring 1966, 1965, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    3 1142 04225396 6
  - Abby Weed Grey reading from Gallway Kinnell 8/6/75 report today, Aug 6, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Parviz, Sia, & Abby Weed Grey - April 1964 (see slip), Apr 1964 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Pierce re Janet, Bishop Bayne, Sia re Parviz, Phillips re Banking last of July 1966 Recorder one side (see slip for details) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Abby Weed Grey (side 1 only), undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Mike Milkovich re exhibit of Contemporary Turkish Painting at MCAD 7/17/71(see slip for details), Jul 17, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 1.) Abby Weed Grey - talk to "U" writer's group 10/12/64 2.) Parviz re Prophet April 13, 1963, 1963, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Original Tape, Mrs. Grey or Smithsonian, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - 2 Reels -August 12, 1975 CTA thru Jan. 6, 1963, 1963, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Workout on Talks 1965 Jan 5 "Poets & Prophets from Athens to Katmandu"- St. Louis Pk Woman's Club Jan 6 "Communication Thru Art" - New Century Club- gallery talk (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Nov. 1964 1.) Herstand- conclusion Nov. 11, 1964 re India Art Festival Munzner on ("Genesis-Nov.") Sia Armajani ("Caligraphy") 2.) Peg Cogswell, Steb Bowles, Peg on… (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous 1963- a notebook with notes pertaining to contents of the reel accompanied (See sleeve 33a-for notebook) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Notebook-notes on content of reel 33 and other reels (?), undated (Box 11, Folder 33a)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - ? Iranian-drums-etc.? (larger reel), undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Mrs. Grey 1/4 " Master and Transfer (Not on a reel), undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Writer's Conference #2, 7/17/69 Kinnell, Grey Lecture, Jul 17, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225397 4
    7" reel
  - Grey Memorial Lecture-Writer's Conference 6/15/64, University of Utah Andrew Lytle (slip enclosed), Jun 15, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bettina Corke's Poet & Philosopher, Final Mix, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    7" reel. This tape has been digitized.
  - Lecture in English "American Painting & Sculpture in the U.S." given by Robert M. Gollinpe, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Iranian Music, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Summer Writer's Conference #1, 7/17/69 Kinnell-Grey Lecture, Jul 17, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - B.E. Grey Memorial Lecture Mrs. Stanford -Reel 1, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1970 Grey Lecture - Reel 1, Part I (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1970 Grey Lecture - Reel 2, Part II (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Lecture in Turkish read by Kerin Ausar for the exhibit on American Painting and sculpture in the U.S., undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Margaret Cornelius' Batiks showing at American Center-Lahore, Jan 14, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bogata, 6/13/69, Jun 13, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Footage - Print Minneapolis Young Graphics. Mrs. Grey (in shipping container), undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Footage - Print Minneapolis Young Graphics. Mrs. Grey (in unmarked shipping container), undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - WILL (sides 1 & 2), Jun 22, 1977 (Box 12, Cassette 1)
    Audio Cassette
  - 1) Set 50 2) Set 51, undated (Box 12, Cassette 2)
  - Aug. 20, 1975 (Box 12, Cassette 3)